BAYAN HAMMADEH

Back End Developer

Back-end developer with 5+ years of back-end development. Build web applications, which are fit for purpose, functionally correct and meets the user's precise needs. I have a record of accomplishment of using new technologies to bring software products to life. On a personal level, I am full of energy and passion. Right now, I would like to join a company where there is a culture of encouragement, respect and teamwork.

Contact Information

Phone

+963940212527

Email

bayanahammadeh@gmail.com

Github

- https://github.com/bayanahammadeh
 LinkedIn
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/bayan-hammadeh-7b9113220

Education

DAMASCUS UNIVERSITY

Information Technology Engineering

Skills

PHP, Laravel, JavaScript, MySQL, HTML, Bootstrap, CSS, Linux, Basics of CEH.

Work Experiences

NANS -- DAMASCUS, SYRIA, 2016 to Present

FULL STACK Developer

- Experience in front-end development, code the front-end of a website, bring the web designer's design to life, and ensure responsive design.
- Experience in back-end development, work behind the scene, building and maintain the technology needed to power the front-end, ensure that everything the front-end developer builds is fully functional.
- Create and manage the database.

VULNERABILITY SCANNING TOOLS

 Experience in using Vulnerability scanning tools like, Yaazhini, Ostorlab, Wireshark, Acunetix, Burp suite

LINUX

Ability writing Linux script.

AGRICULTURE MINISTRY -- DAMASCUS, SYRIA, 2007 to 2015

DESKTOP APPLICATION PRGRAMMING

Programming several desktop programs.

CIDAR COMPANY -- DAMASCUS, SYRIA, 2006 to 2007

DESKTOP APPLICATION PRGRAMMING

 Programming desktop program to manage all accounting operations and warehouse management.

Completed projects

TOOLS

https://tools.ecc.sy/

Tools is a web application that offers many services such as generate certificate signing requests (CSRs), generate public/private keys, view "digital certificate or csr" properties, in addition to many other features. User-friendly interface, advanced features.

Developed with Laravel, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and JavaScript.

CV

https://github.com/bayanahammadeh/cv

CV is a Bayan Hammmadeh Portfolio
Developed with Laravel, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and JavaScript.

Ecommerce

https://github.com/bayanahammadeh/ecommerce

Ecommerce is a web application that provides many services such as view products and the possibility of purchasing them In addition to many other features.

Developed with Laravel, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and JavaScript.

Courses and Qualifications

NANS -- Damascus, Syria --2018

Basics of Network

NANS -- Damascus, Syria --2018

Basics of Linux

NANS -- Damascus, Syria --2018

Advance of Linux

MOSCOW, RUSSIA --2019

Public key infrastructure

SSS -- Damascus, Syria --2020

Basics of CEH

SSS -- Damascus, Syria --2020

Basics of PYTHON

Languages

Arabic English